{
"name": "8급한자",
"cards":
[{"question":"校","answer":"학교 교"},
{"question":"敎","answer":"가르칠 교"},
{"question":"九","answer":"아홉 구"},
{"question":"國","answer":"나라 국"},
{"question":"軍","answer":"군사 군"},
{"question":"金","answer":"쇠 금, 성 김"},
{"question":"南","answer":"남녘 남"},
{"question":"女","answer":"계집 녀"},
{"question":"年","answer":"해 년"},
{"question":"大","answer":"큰 대"},
{"question":"東","answer":"동녘 동"},
{"question":"六","answer":"여섯 륙"},
{"question":"萬","answer":"일만 만"},
{"question":"母","answer":"어미 모"},
{"question":"木","answer":"나무 목"},
{"question":"門","answer":"문 문"},
{"question":"民","answer":"백성 민"},
{"question":"白","answer":"흰 백"},
{"question":"父","answer":"아비 부"},
{"question":"北","answer":"북녘 북, 달아날 배"},
{"question":"四","answer":"넉 사"},
{"question":"山","answer":"메[뫼] 산"},
{"question":"三","answer":"석 삼"},
{"question":"生","answer":"날 생"},
{"question":"西","answer":"서녘 서"},
{"question":"先","answer":"먼저 선"},
{"question":"小","answer":"작을 소"},
{"question":"水","answer":"물 수"},
{"question":"室","answer":"집 실"},
{"question":"十","answer":"열 십"},
{"question":"五","answer":"다섯 오"},
{"question":"王","answer":"임금 왕"},
{"question":"外","answer":"바깥 외"},
{"question":"月","answer":"달 월"},
{"question":"二","answer":"두 이"},
{"question":"人","answer":"사람 인"},
{"question":"一","answer":"한 일"},
{"question":"日","answer":"날 일"},
{"question":"長","answer":"긴 장"},
{"question":"弟","answer":"아우 제"},
{"question":"中","answer":"가운데 중"},
{"question":"靑","answer":"푸를 청"},
{"question":"寸","answer":"마디 촌"},
{"question":"七","answer":"일곱 칠"},
{"question":"土","answer":"흙 토"},
{"question":"八","answer":"여덟 팔"},
{"question":"學","answer":"배울 학"},
{"question":"韓","answer":"한국 한, 나라 한"},
{"question":"兄","answer":"형 형"},
{"question":"火","answer":"불 화"}]
}
